This video is for you to introduce the update about the user interface
After the update to 2025.0, our default library window will be changed to a new library
About the use of the new library, you can check the explanation in the new function in 2024.2
If you want to go back to the old library, you can also click the return key here to return to the old library
In 2025.0, we added the collector function before the transfer
This function will make the transfer of the collector faster
Quickly build your own familiar workstation
In the current old library, there is a new collector from the 2024.2 version
Now switch back to the new library
Click the add button, you can see two options
Create a new library and the collector before the transfer
Choose the collector before the transfer
Now you can see that the new library has been added to the new library
When you right-click on the collector or file
You can find that there is one more option here
It is displayed in the resource manager
It can help you find the path where the file is located more quickly
This operation is also applicable to the old library
Through this function, you do not need to re-add all the collectors
In the new library, you can quickly complete this operation
In the previous version
The window selection card will be reset after switching modes
And the UV editor and 2D window cannot be displayed at the same time
So we have to go back to the simulation mode first to see the 2D window
This is not convenient during the editing process
In 2025.0, the UV and animation editor will be reset from the window mode
So we can use other tools or windows without switching modes
The UV editor is now at the top of the menu
In the 3D material UV selection card
Just like the animation editor, open the UV editor now
You can also freely switch to other windows to edit
This function saves additional steps in the switching mode
Make the editing process faster
Since 2025.0
We support the display settings in the 3D and 2D vertical menu bar
Preserved in the project file
Let's take a look at it together
If the window is a new project
Open the created project at this time
It will automatically apply its display settings
If the window has already opened the project
When opening another project
You can select display settings to open this file
3D and 2D vertical menu bar information display
Or maintain the default settings of the software
Need to explain
Display settings are currently only supported in the project file
The files saved in the previous version do not contain the display settings
In the subsequent update
The clothing file will also support the selection of this information
Hope this function update
Can maximize the reduction of file creators
And the error of the receiver in checking the 3D file effect
Because the icon of the project file is displayed in the shrink chart
After updating to 2025.0
When saving files
Do not use the PNG shrink chart of the other file
If you want to save the shrink chart
You can set it in the user self-definition setting
In the main menu bar
Find the user self-definition at the bottom of the settings
Then click on the default file
You can set whether to save the shrink chart at the bottom of the project
The default is not selected
After selecting, you can see that the type selection box will pop up
You can choose the type of shrink chart here
Choose the current view
The saved shrink chart is the same as the shrink chart in the previous version
The shrink chart in the previous version is the same as the shrink chart in the previous version
Select the front and back left of the four views
You will get a multi-view with four views
Please note that the view will automatically adjust to adapt to the clothing itself
And does not include models
Therefore, if you choose this option
It is recommended to hide the model
After selecting the self-definition view
You can open the multi-view setting file
And save the selected options according to the settings
In this case, it is also recommended that you hide the model
If the selection is changed to all clothing
When saving, it will be saved as the main body of clothing
This setting can help you freely choose whether to save
And how to save the shrink chart of the project file
I hope this can help you improve your work efficiency